Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibitions and Projects, 108529
  - Touch Sanitation Show - Marine Transfer Station, 59th St, Sep 9 - Oct 5, 1984, 108736 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Nighttrippers - The Russian Baths, First Baptist Church, Oscar Hammerstein Opera House, Dec 1, 8, 15, 1984, 108735 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Promo - general, 1984; 108734 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Publication - Insights / On Sites: Perspectives on Art in Public Places [Creative Time article by Anita Contini], published by Partners for Livable Places, 1984, 108733 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Clipping - Di Suvero Lithograph sale for Creative Time, 1984; 108732 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Promo - envelope for Creative Time, designed by Anton van Dalen, [1984]; 108731 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Art in the Anchorage 2 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, May 15 - June 30, 1985, 108730 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Publications - [Art in the Anchorage articles] Bijutsu Techo Monthly Art Magazine 8/85 (vol.37, no.549); Art in Action, published by Sogetsu-kai Foundation, Tokyo, 1985, 108729 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Art on the Beach 7 - Battery Park City Landfill, July 2 - Sep 13, 1985, 108728 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Original drawings - Art on the Beach 7, 1985; 108727 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Publications - [Art on the Beach articles] New Art Examiner magazine 8/85; Smithsonian magazine 12/85; Modo magazine no.76, 1985, 108726 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Publications - [Art on the Beach articles] Ear magazine, Fall 1985; Graffiti magazine 11/85, 108725 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - A Drop in the Bucket - Franklin St park, Sep 5 - Nov 5, 1985, 108724 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Press - general, 1985; 108723 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Promo - Creative Time Benefit Art Sale and Party, Christie's, 1985; 108722 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Promo - The Creative Times (Vol.1, Issue 2), 1985; 108721 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Promo - holiday greeting card, designed by Calvin Reid, 1985; 108720 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - B. Holden to Diderot - US Federal Courthouse, Foley Square, Mar 10 - June 20, 1986, 108719 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Publication - [B. Holden to Diderot Article] Arts Magazine 10/86, 1986; 108718 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Art in the Anchorage 3: The Memory Theatre of Giulio Camillo - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, June 6 - July 13, 1986, 108717 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Jazz in the Anchorage [Art in the Anchorage 3] - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, June 8 - 29, 1986, 108716 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Performance in the Park 1 - Central Park Bandshell, Aug 3 - Sep 14, 1986, 108715 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Press - general, 1986; 108714 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence - general, 1986; 108713 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Promo - holiday greeting card, designed by David Humphrey, 1986; 108712 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Press/Promo - Cee Scott Brown appointment as Executive Director, January 1987, 108711 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Gala Benefit - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, June 1987, 108710 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Art in the Anchorage 4 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, June - July, 1987, 108709 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Performance in the Park 2 - Central Park Bandshell, June 19 - Sep 11, 1987, 108708 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Art on the Beach 8 - Hunter's Point, Queens, July 24 - Sep 20, 1987, 108707 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Project Packets - Art on the Beach 8, 1987; 108706 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Publications - [Art on the Beach 8 article] Off Ramp magazine, Spring 1988 (vol.1, No.1), 1987; 108705 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Press - general, 1987-1988; 108704 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Publication - Creative Time retrospective catalog (1987-1988), 108703 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - In the WINTER GARDEN: Anggrek; Relay - World Financial Center Winter Garden, May 10-11, 1988; May 17-18, 1988, 108702 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Misfortunes of Desire Acted Out - Shea Stadium Parking Lot, May 17, 1988, 108701 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Art in the Anchorage 5 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, June 10 - July 27, 1988, 108700 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Art on the Beach 9 - Hunter's Point, Queens, July 15 - Sep 18, 1988, 108699 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - 15th Anniversary Halloween Party, Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, Oct 29, 1988, 108698 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - UP Tiempo!: Performing and Visual Artists of the Americas - El Museo del Barrio, Nov 4 - Dec 10, 1988, 108697 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Promo - Creative Time 15th anniversary fund and party mailing, 1988; 108696 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Promo - Spring and Summer Events mailing, 1988; 108695 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Publication - The First NY International Festival of the Arts program book, published 1988, 108694 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Misc - project proposal guidelines, 1988; 108693 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Planning/Correspondence - Battery Maritime Building project, 1988-1991; 108692 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Planning/Correspondence - Battery Maritime Building project, 1988-1991; 108691 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Publication - Battery Maritime Building reference book, compiled by NYC Dept of Transportation and Bureau of Planning and Research, [1988]; 108690 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Proposal - for Battery Maritime Building, South Ferry Center for the Arts, by Creative Time and Dance Theater Workshop, Inc., 1988; 108689 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Planning - Battery Maritime Building financial and legal records, 1989-1990; 108688 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence - general, 1988; 108687 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Citywide - April - May, 1989, 108686 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Poets in the Bars - citywide, Apr 6 - May 1, 1989, 108685 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Light Site-ings: Holland Tunnel Drive-In Billboard - Holland Tunnel, Apr 13 - 16, 1989, 108684 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Publication - Holland Tunnel Key newspaper, [1989]; 108683 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Automotive Votive - citywide, May 6 - 29, 1989, 108682 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Kissing Doesn't Kill: Greed and Indifference Do - citywide, June - Dec 1989, 108681 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Publications - [Kissing Doesn't Kill features] Outlook magazine, Summer '90 (no.9); Blueprint magazine, Jul - Aug '90 (no.69), 1989; 108680 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Art in the Anchorage 6 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, June 22 - Aug 13, 1989, 108679 (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 1 - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, Aug 13 - 16, 1989, 108678 (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Video/Musica - 26 Avenue B, Nov 17 - 19, 1989, 108677 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - It Was Only Art - citywide, Oct 1989, 108676 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - What's In a Flame? - Cable Building, Nov 23 - Dec 3, 1989, 108675 (Box 3, Folder 113A)
  - What's In a Flame? - Project Mock-Up, 1989; 108674 (Box 3, Folder 113B)
  - Visual AIDS: A Day Without Art - Dec 1, 1989, 108673 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Public Information - citywide, "dates to be announced", 1989; 108672 (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Press - general, 1989; 108671 (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Correspondence - general, 1989; 108670 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Promo - Summer Events mailing, 1989; 108669 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Publication - Creative Time retrospective catalog (1989-1990), 108668 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Creative Time at Dixon Place - 64 East 4th St, Apr 24 - 26, 1990, 108667 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - The Black Sheep - First Ave between 1st and Houston, May 1990 - Apr 1991, 1990-1991; 108666 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - The Wilds and the Deep - Battery Maritime Building, May 25 - June 24, 1990, 108665 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Press Packet - South Ferry Center for the Arts, The Wilds and the Deep, 1990; 108664 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Art in the Anchorage 7 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, July 13 - Oct 7, 1990, 108663 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Publication - [Art in the Anchorage article] High Performance magazine, Spring 1991, 1990; 108662 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Original drawing - Nancy Rubins [Art in the Anchorage 7], 1990; 108661 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 2 - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, Aug 11 - 18, 1990, 108660 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Surgeon General's Warning - citywide, Sep - Nov, 1990, 108659 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - The Bowery Concert - Sarah D. Roosevelt Park, Sep 15, 1990, 108658 (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Clipping - Cincinnati Contemporary Arts Center, Oct 30, 1990, 108657 (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Carbon Monoxide is a Lethal Gas - citywide, Oct - Nov 1990, 108656 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Press Release - "Creative Time refuses to sign restrictive NEA contracts", Oct 1, 1990, 108655 (Box 3, Folder 132)
  - Press Release - "Nan Goldin refuses to sign restrictive NEA contracts", Oct 1, 1990, 108654 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Love of a Poet - Battery Maritime Building, Oct 10 - 13, 17 - 20, 1990, 108653 (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Day Without Art: Electric Blanket - The Cooper Union, 3rd Ave and 7th St, Dec 1, 1990, 108652 (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - Publication - "A Threnody for Street Kids" brochure, by David Levi Strauss, [1990]; 108651 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Press packet - general, 1990; 108650 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Correspondence - general, 1990; 108649 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Publication - [Creative Time feature] Frame Magazine no.2, 1990, 108648 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Proposal guidelines - for Creative Time Citywide projects, 1990; 108647 (Box 3, Folder 140)
  - Promo - Summer Events mailing, 1990; 108646 (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Publication - The Dance Theater Workshop New(s) in Revue, Vol.XXV Issue 3, Spring events 1990, 108645 (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - Sample letter to public officials on NEA Funding, 1990; 108644 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Press Release - Art Matters Inc., on support of visual arts funding, Feb 1991, 108643 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - Visualize This - citywide, Apr 1991 - Apr 1993, 1991-1993; 108642 (Box 3, Folder 145)
  - Publication - [Visualize This article] i-D Magazine, no.97, Oct 1991, 108641 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Angels Have Been Sent to Me - citywide, May 1991, 108640 (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Black Works - The Kitchen, 512 W 19th St, May 1 - 4, 1991, 108639 (Box 3, Folder 148)
  - Publication - [Black Works] Mickery: Pictorial II, 1988-199, published by Stichting Mickery Workshop, 1991, 108638 (Box 3, Folder 149)
  - The Most Exciting Women in Music - citywide, June 1991, 108637 (Box 3, Folder 150)
  - Publication - [Most Exciting… article] XS magazine, June 26, 1991, 108636 (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - Not Just the Parade - citywide, June 1991, 108635 (Box 3, Folder 152)
  - The Honeymoon Project - World Financial Center Winter Garden, June 7 - 30, 1991, 108634 (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Suz/o/Suz - Kaufman-Astoria Studios, June 12 - 15, 1991, 108633 (Box 3, Folder 154)
  - Memories of New York Chinatown - 70 Mulberry St, June 23, 1991, 108632 (Box 3, Folder 155)
  - Art in the Anchorage 8 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, July 10 - Sep 7, 1991, 108631 (Box 3, Folder 156)
  - Sounds in the Anchorage [Art in the Anchorage 8] - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, July 10 - Sep 7, 1991, 108630 (Box 3, Folder 157)
  - Skin - Lincoln Center, Aug 23, 1991, 108629 (Box 3, Folder 158)
  - Wigstock - Union Square Park, Sep 2, 1991, 108628 (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - Masterpieces Without the Director - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, Sep 28 - 29, 1991, 108627 (Box 3, Folder 160)
  - Clean Needles Save Lives - citywide via television, Oct 1991, 108626 (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - As a Dream That Vanishes - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, Oct 30 - Nov 24, 1991, 108625 (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - Fear of Disclosure: (In)visible Women - citywide, Dec 1, 1991, 108624 (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Our Voices: Our Songs - 208 W 13th St, Dec 27, 1991, 108623 (Box 4, Folder 164)
  - Citywide - 1991 proposal guidelines, 108622 (Box 4, Folder 165)
  - Promo - Creative Time mailing holiday mailing, 1991; 108621 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - Citywide - project listings, 1991; 108620 (Box 4, Folder 167)
  - Publication - ["Public Art in Manhattan" article] Domus magazine, no.723, Jan 1991, 108619 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - Press packet - general, 1991; 108618 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - Correspondence - general, 1991; 108617 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - Publication - Creative Time retrospective catalogue, 1991-1992, published by Creative Time in 1993, 108616 (Box 4, Folder 171)
  - Fear of Disclosure - 1991-1993 project info (see also individual projects), 108615 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - Publication - "Just the Facts" domestic violence pamphlet, Jan 1992, 108614 (Box 4, Folder 173)
  - Domestic Violence Milk Carton Project - citywide via milk carton, Jan - Feb 1992, 108613 (Box 4, Folder 174)
  - Milk cartons - set of four milk cartons for Domestic Violence Milk Carton Project, Jan - Feb, 1992, 108612 (Box 4, Folder 175)
  - Use Mass Transit 1: A Billboard Project - citywide via billboard, Jan - Feb 1992, 108611 (Box 4, Folder 176)
  - Roy Cohn/Jack Smith - 33 Wooster St., Jan 24 - Feb 16, 1992, 108610 (Box 4, Folder 177)
  - Private/Public - New York City subway lines, Mar 26 - May 1, 1992, 108609 (Box 4, Folder 178)
  - Transitions, Inc. - citywide, May 8 - 9, 1992, 108608 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - Sacrificial Ornament - Municipal Art Society, May 21 - June 27, 1992, 108607 (Box 4, Folder 180)
  - Publication - Sacrificial Ornament exhibition catalogue, published by Southern Alberta Art Gallery, 1992, 108606 (Box 4, Folder 181)
  - Art in the Anchorage 9: Women's Action Coalition - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, July 10 - Sep 20, 1992, 108605 (Box 4, Folder 182)
  - A Surreal Soap Opera - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, Aug 20, 1992, 108604 (Box 4, Folder 183)
  - Press Release - from Dance Theater Workshop, 9th Annual Bessie Awards, Sep 9, 1992, 108603 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - Accountability? - NYC, Chicago, Los Angeles, Oct 1992, 108602 (Box 4, Folder 185)
  - Underdevelopment in Progress/ 500 Years - Soho 20 Gallery, 469 Broome St, Oct 1992, Sep 28 - Oct 23, 1993, 1992, 1993; 108601 (Box 4, Folder 186)
  - Two Spirits Speak Out - Grand Central Station, Nov 21, 1992, 108600 (Box 4, Folder 187)
  - Use Mass Transit 2 - citywide via billboard, Dec 1992 - Feb 1993, 1992-1993; 108599 (Box 4, Folder 188)
  - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program - citywide via television, Dec 1, 1992, 108598 (Box 4, Folder 189)
  - Fear of Disclosure: Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien - 52 W 8th St, citywide, 1992; 108597 (Box 4, Folder 190)
  - Clippings - misc NEA articles, 1992; 108596 (Box 4, Folder 191)
  - Correspondence - general, 1992; 108595 (Box 4, Folder 192)
  - Higher Ground - 268 Mulberry St, Jan 9 - 30, 1993, 108594 (Box 4, Folder 193)
  - Victory Music Series - New Victory Theater, Apr 3 - 24, 1993, 108593 (Box 4, Folder 194)
  - Hairy Tales - citywide, Apr 7 - 22, 1993, 108592 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - Art in the Anchorage 10 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, June 4 - Sep 25, 1993, 108591 (Box 4, Folder 196)
  - Publication - [Art in the Anchorage 10, Ringside article] Lighting Dimensions magazine, Nov 1993, 108590 (Box 4, Folder 197)
  - Publication - [Art in the Anchorage 10, Ringside article] Dance Ink magazine, Winter 1993, 108589 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Publication - [Art in the Anchorage 10, Ringside article] Dans Tidningen magazine, No.4, 1993, 108588 (Box 4, Folder 199)
  - In Honor of Allen R. Schindler - citywide, July 1993, 108587 (Box 4, Folder 200)
  - 42nd St Art Project - proposals, sketches, descriptions, etc, July 8 - Nov, 1993; 108586 (Box 4, Folder 201)
  - 42nd St Art Project - production materials, 1993; 108585 (Box 4, Folder 202)
  - 42nd St Art Project - promotional materials, 1993; 108584 (Box 4, Folder 203)
  - 42nd St Art Project - press, 1993; 108583 (Box 4, Folder 204)
  - 42nd St Art Project - press packet, 1993; 108582 (Box 4, Folder 205)
  - 42nd St Art Project - correspondence, 1993; 108581 (Box 4, Folder 206)
  - Universal Family Album - 30 Lincoln Center Plaza, Aug 14 - 15, 1993, 108580 (Box 4, Folder 207)
  - Day Without Art: We Interrupt This Program - citywide via television, Dec 1, 1993, 108579 (Box 4, Folder 208)
  - Just Outside the City - 1993-1995, 108578 (Box 4, Folder 209)
  - Correspondence - big women photo, 1993; 108577 (Box 4, Folder 210)
  - Publication - Creative Time retrospective catalogue, 1993-1994, published by Creative Time 1995, 108576 (Box 4, Folder 211)
  - Press Packet - Dumb Type, 1993; 108575 (Box 4, Folder 212)
  - Correspondence - general, 1993; 108574 (Box 4, Folder 213)
  - Body Politics - Great Hall, The Cooper Union, Feb 14 - 15, 1994, 108573 (Box 5, Folder 214)
  - Mass Transit 3: Hey Bozo… - citywide via billboard, May 1994, 108572 (Box 5, Folder 215)
  - Fear of Disclosure: Out in Silence and Not a Simple Story - citywide, June 5, 7, 1994, 108571 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress - 45 Greene St, June 7 - July 1, 1994, 108570 (Box 5, Folder 217)
  - Patina du Prey's Memorial Dress - sign/comment book, 1994; 108569 (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - Master Builder - Chelsea, July, Dec 1994, 108568 (Box 5, Folder 219)
  - 42nd St Art Project - 42nd St Development Project, Inc. request for proposals booklet, May 16, 1994, 108567 (Box 5, Folder 220)
  - 42nd St Art Project - Proposals, sketches, planning, etc, 1994, 108566 (Box 5, Folder 221)
  - 42nd St Art Project - Production materials, 1994; 108565 (Box 5, Folder 222)
  - 42nd St Art Project - promotional materials, 1994; 108564 (Box 5, Folder 223)
  - 42nd St Art project - Haikus, 1994; 108563 (Box 5, Folder 224)
  - 42nd St Art Project - media coverage, press packets, 1994; 108562 (Box 5, Folder 225)
  - 42nd St Art Project - press, 1994; 108561 (Box 5, Folder 226)
  - 42nd St Art Project - correspondence, 1994; 108560 (Box 5, Folder 227)
  - Publication/clipping - [42nd St Art Project features] Public Art Review magazine (Issue 10, vol.5, no.2); Philadelphia Inquirer (5/10/94), 1994; 108559 (Box 5, Folder 228)
  - Art in the Anchorage 11: Mirage - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, July - Sep 1994, 108558 (Box 5, Folder 229)
  - Publication - [Art in the Anchorage review] - Dance Magazine (12/94), 1994; 108557 (Box 5, Folder 230)
  - 20th Anniversary Celebration - Apollo Theater, July 7, 1994, 108556 (Box 5, Folder 231)
  - First Annual Sara D. Roosevelt Park Summer Festival - Sara D. Roosevelt Park, July 10, 1994, 108555 (Box 5, Folder 232)
  - Lincoln Center Out of Doors: Wild Style - 30 Lincoln Plaza, Aug 10, 1994, 108554 (Box 5, Folder 233)
  - Combat Zone: Campaign HQ Against Domestic Violence - 110 Mercer St, Oct - Dec 1994, 108553 (Box 5, Folder 234)
  - Proposals/Planning - Citywide panel proposal review, Nov 1, 1994, 108552 (Box 5, Folder 235)
  - Clippings - Day Without Art 1994, 108551 (Box 5, Folder 236)
  - Planning/Correspondence - Barney's New York Window Project, 1994; 108550 (Box 5, Folder 237)
  - Publication - [Creative Time feature by Alyson Pou] Movement Research Performance Journal no.9 (Fall/Winter 1994), 108549 (Box 5, Folder 238)
  - Press - general, 1994; 108548 (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - Correspondence - general, 1994; 108547 (Box 5, Folder 240)
  - Art in the Anchorage - proposals, planning, and production materials, 1995; 108546 (Box 5, Folder 241)
  - Deviant Craft - [Art in the Anchorage] planning/production materials, 1995; 108545 (Box 5, Folder 242)
  - Press packet - Vintage: Families of Value, a film by Thomas Allen Harris, 1995; 108544 (Box 5, Folder 243)
  - Rent-a-Body - citywide, Feb - July, 1996, 108543 (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - 1-900-ALL-KAREN - international via telephone, Feb 16 - Aug 16, 1998, 108542 (Box 5, Folder 245)
  - Between Dreams and History - Ludlow and Rivington St, Oct 22 - Nov 14, 1998, 108541 (Box 5, Folder 246)
  - Art in the Anchorage 18 - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage, May 31 - July 29, 2001, 108540 (Box 5, Folder 247)
  - Untitled [Poster campaign] - citywide, Mar 11 - 25, 2002, 108539 (Box 5, Folder 248)
  - Winter in the Fall Benefit - Ritz Carlton, Battery Park City, Oct 15, 2002, 108538 (Box 5, Folder 249)
  - The Peace Piece - citywide, Mar 20, 2003, 108537 (Box 5, Folder 250)
  - Correspondence - general, 2003; 108536 (Box 5, Folder 251)
  - Imitation of Christ - citywide, Sep 8 - 15, 2004, 108535 (Box 5, Folder 252)
  - Promo - "Consumer's Guide to Times Square Advertising" handout, by Creative Time, 2004; 108534 (Box 5, Folder 253)
  - 59th Minute - Times Square Panasonic Astrovision, Mar 7 - Jun 5, 2006, 108533 (Box 5, Folder 254)
  - Creative Time Book planning and notes, 2006; 108532 (Box 5, Folder 255)
  - Correspondence - general, 2006; 108531 (Box 5, Folder 256)
  - Undated/unidentified material - postcard; letter, 108530 (Box 5, Folder 257)
- Series II: Grants, Development, and Financial Correspondence, 108324
  This series is divided into seven subseries and consists of financial records, grant proposals, budget documentation, correspondence, and ancillary supporting documentation. Originally arranged chronological by fiscal year, material has been re-organized to group chronologically by year as well as by grant funding agency. The content within individual folders reflects Creative Time's original order.
  - Subseries A: NEA Grants, 108409
    - NEA - Special Projects, rejection [Red Grooms, Ruckus Manhattan], 1974-1976; 108528 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      General
      Offsite Barcode: 31142042233620
    - NEA - Artist in Residence Program, #R 60-41-7C [Ruckus Manhattan], 1975; 108527 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - NEA - City Spirit Grant, 1975; 108526 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - NEA - Art in Public Places, rejection [Charlie Ross, Prism Sculpture], 1976; 108525 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - NEA - Public Education and Awareness Program [Ruckus Manhattan], 1976; 108524 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - NEA - Artist in Residence Program, #R70-41-15C, #R70-41-15B [Rockne Krebs, Light Sculpture], 1976-1978; 108523 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - NEA - Artist in Residence Program, #RQ0-41-9C [Otto Piene, Anemones], 1976-1978; 108522 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, Workshops/Alternative Spaces, #R70-41-153, 1976-1978; 108521 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - NEA - Artist in Residence Program, #R70-41-3890, #R70-41-389C [Custom and Culture], 1977-1978; 108520 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - NEA - Visual Art in the Performing Arts, #R70-41-422C [Butler's Lives of the Saints], 1977-1978; 108519 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - NEA - Services to the Field, #R70-41-332 [documentation brochure], 1977-1979; 108518 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - NEA - Documentation and Resource Program, #R80-41-308 [documentation brochure], 1978-1979; 108517 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, Workshops/Alternative Spaces, #R80-41-66 [Art on the Beach, Downtown Drive-in], 1978-1979; 108516 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - NEA - Services to the Field, #92-4137-340 [Documentation and Resource Center], 1979-1980; 108515 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, Workshops/Alternative Spaces, #92-4118-104, 1979-1980; 108514 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - NEA - Museum Program, Special Exhibitions, rejection [Bill Brand, Masstransiscope], 1979; 108513 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - NEA - Museum Program, Special Exhibitions, #02-4442-107 [Art on the Beach], 1979-1980; 108512 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - NEA - Museum Program, Special Exhibitions, #92-2022-121 [Custom and Culture], 1979-1980; 108511 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - NEA - Art in Public Places, #02-4140-791 [Bill Brand, Masstransiscope], 1979-1981; 108510 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, consulting, site evaluation, etc., 1980; 108509 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - NEA - Inter-Arts, Special Projects, Arts Centers and Festivals, #12-5440-008, 1980; 108508 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - NEA - Museum Program, Special Exhibitions, #12-4442-165 [Art on the Beach], 1980-1981; 108507 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - NEA - Art in Public Places, [Liz Philips, Windspun], 1980-1981; 108506 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, #02-4120-193 [Art on the Beach, Masstransiscope, Projects at the Precinct, Windspun], 1980-1981; 108505 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - NEA - Visual Arts, Services to the Field, #02-4123-1064 [documentation, Resource Center, travel], 1980-1981; 108504 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - NEA - Design Arts, rejection [Art in Urban Design, Mierle Laderman Ukeles], 1981; 108503 (Box 6, Folder 26)